

Date of Birth: 29/01/1990 | 052-6740710 | matan3sh@gmail.com

About Me

I'm 29 years old, highly motivated, loves to work in a team and fast learner. I've always been on the technical side and I really love it. I can testify to myself that I have a passion for high tech, an analytical mindset, productive, creative ability and always pay attention to details.

Education

- SCE COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING | BEER SHEVA | 2015 2019 | BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING
- TECHNOLOGICAL COLLEGE | BEER SHEVA | 2008-2010 | PRACTICAL ENGINEER-ELECTRONICS
- ITZHAK RAGER HIGH SCHOOL | 2003 2008 | COMPUTER SOFTWARE MAJOR

Skills & Abilities

KNOWLEDGE:

- Familiar with Programming Languages: C, C++, C#, JAVA, PYTHON and Oracle SQL Developer.
- Knowledge at Assembly, **Object-Oriented** and **Multi-Threaded** programming proficient with **Design Patterns**, **Bash Scripting** in **Linux\Unix** operation system.
- Basic understanding in cryptographic mechanisms underlying in Blockchain technology, implement a smart contract in Solidity on the Ethereum Virtual Machine.
- Self-Learning: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript focused on ReactJS, NextJS, VueJS framework and Cross-Platform mobile apps using React Native.
- Experience working with Firebase, Mongo databases.

PROJECTS DEGREE:

- Final Project: Departmental excellence project [score 95]- development a social network
 app revolution for wandering and lost pets, based React Native using Firebase for a
 database.
 - o Received a social scholarship and selected project at the **2019 Engineers Society**.
- Build a computer store management software based C programming language.
- Develop a Pets Shop essentials DApp **Solidity**, **Truffle Framework and Ganache** as a virtual blockchain machine using **Metamask** as Ethereum wallet and **ReactJS** as client side.
- Develop an Internet online shopping store based ReactJS client side and NodeJS server side, using Redux to keep data flow clear and predictable.

Work Experience

PROJECTION ROOM MANAGER | 2016-2018 | Yes Planet Cinema Beer- Sheva

- Full-Time Job (100% during my degree studies) Manage a crew of eight people.
- Responsibility for all film programs and cinema technical system.
- Weekly communication with the IMAX in Canada and 4DX in South Korea.
- FREELANCE DEVELOPER:
 - Management platform for Projection Room department in Yes Planet Beer-Sheva, based on JAVA programming language, JAVA GUI system (NetBeans) and database used my SQL Server Management Studio.

Army

TECHNICIAN OF ELECTRONIC WARFARE SYSTEMS | 2010-2013 | Full military service

- A six months Course Electronic warfare systems technician.
 - Expertise and experience in RF electronics.
 - Training in designated warfare systems: Elta, Tadiran Systems and Netline.
 - Working under pressure in operational activities and exercises.

LANGUAGES:

• Hebrew – mother tongue | English – fluently

Recommendations will be provided upon requests.